Like the candle hit the stream
Linners on the altar
The portal's open, no place to hide
And nobody falters
Tricks walk through the tarot spread
The magic's coming through
To the transmission, yeah
That means you
Buy your sale tonight
Beast kid again
Come running, got the band tonight
She got compass and a claws girl
the whole chat screaming beater come back one more time thunder at the window nancy rodin on the
rain pull the magician manifest and defendants like his name don't even know his panel box
toes again and lost and there we go officer alex mcqueen your man smoke machine and coughs
controlling dags i'm off the plate i caught him in the light who i wanted him to be not who he
I'm so hurt. Here's what a dead channel is a dead channel is a channel like that first of all
You can't broadcast on second of all no one can see so already. I mean at least with one person in there
I know when or can you bring the people in here, please? We need you cats. Where are you sitting?
We're sitting on my shoulder. Oh my god. You want to go in there? What are you doing?
So no matter how dead it is, it's not as dead as your YouTube channel RG
These minds still here. Okay. Anyhow
Yeah, I'm trying to figure out the TTS
Stuff I'm like got it pretty cool. I mean I designed this whole graphical interface and stuff
But I need some like, you know
Help figuring out the thing. Hi. What are you doing?
But you can see I am on my tripod and I level I need to go more I love
What's I love right where my eyes are a little to it I think higher higher higher there we go
Okay, this is my new face.
This is a bad face, I want this to be my face.
What are you doing, Rudy?
You wanna come over here, Rudy?
Where's Lola?
Is Lola behind me?
Hi, Lola.
What are you doing?
Okay, well, let's see what I can do.
Guess I'll chase away the people that hate the music
by playing some music, and then if people like it,
or the people who actually want it here.
Let's do a happy song.
This one's always happy. It's gonna make me smile. I'm out of tobacco, so I'm in a terrible mood. Here we go. Here we go.
This signal survives.
Then I didn't play it today. I didn't put it on the screen today. I keep doing that. I'm so sorry.
Here you go. Excuse me.
Perfect. The people that leave, I don't want to hear it anyway, so that's perfect. All of this is shit, babe.
Our signals we've decoded on Cathedral.
It's a way to signal survive.
Signal survives.
Oh my gosh.
That's so good.
I thought I'd build a profile concept, AI agent.
Well, let's see what's going on.
What do we have on Rumble?
Let me see.
You coming, Ash?
Are you the most beautiful cat?
Are you the most beautiful cat in the world?
Yes.
I like this, because I have better angles now.
Hi.
Like my nails are like, you know, I'm sorry,
they're kind of probably a little dirty.
Hi, how are you? Oh, oh my gosh, aren't I aren't I the worst aren't I the worst? Oh, you love you
Love you love. Oh Lola shout out to Lola everybody. Shout out to beautiful Lola. Oh
You're back. Oh my neck my back. There's sham. Hey, what do we got sham?
That's something cool. Okay, I'm gonna check it out
Check it out right back here
Well, I don't I oh, yeah, hi guys. Is this me who's is it what is this?
I heard this is supposed to be me. Is that is that me? I don't think so. That has to be good times
He has like the overalls, but then look at the others abs and those kind of like are my abs a little bit
I don't know. I don't know who that's supposed to be
Lola, who's that supposed to be?
It's got tits too. Oh my gosh. Hold on
little baby okay it's got tits okay tts or tits well i gotta cancel i'll put it back i'm gonna
watch it here we're gonna go look what i have right here i'll put on um a classic song oh yeah
the image i showed did yep in this day and day hunted stream on every page the shadows laugh
the static sings the phone rings twice nobody's there when it rings the street
Okay, you got breaking breaking news. You have some breaking news everybody. I have a clip. Thank you,
Shan. I just I have to see this. I have to see what's happened on the clip. It looks exciting
already. Already I'm intrigued. Why isn't it downloading? Hold on a second. Virus scan warning.
Oh, it's downloading it.
It's downloading.
Oh my God, it's 1.3 gigabytes.
Hold on.
That's why it's so long.
Okay, okay.
Well, it's going steadily along.
So we'll see.
Uh-oh.
Is he gonna do, he's gonna do a reading for Clumsy?
Oh my gosh.
I know Chris K has done some classic reading.
Actually, he gave me not a bad reading last time.
It wasn't bad.
Some of it was like, what the hell are you talking about?
I mean, but he's like, I love when he goes,
Martha, no, Mary, Margarita, no, Muriel, like, Matt is, I mean, it's like, you don't know
Mary, everyone knows a Mary, right?
Okay, it's like, 20 seconds left, okay, yeah, I jumped the gun, I should have just kept
the video playing, but we have 20 seconds, okay.
And then tomorrow I should have the tts working. I'd love if we can test that out. Oh, hi, babe. Hi, babe
Hi, I love you, baby. Oh, I love you so much. I love you. All right, baby. Okay, baby. Are we ready?
Baby
Okay, you can just share the screen. Okay. I know but I want to down I wanted to download it
So I have it in my archives
Yeah, I got the tts going. It's I mean, it's culto psyche calm that I can go ahead
Well, well, no, hold on buster
Hey motherfucker, how many shuffles you want two or three?
Do I have to choose really? Yeah, two or three. What can it be seven two or three?
I guess I'll choose three everybody choose it. Why is it people choose three for?
Well, it's you only given a fucking couple options, man
Makes it kind of look corny
Corny
He's laughing you said corn
No, I got it. I got a focus when I do the cars because okay
Yeah, you got somebody you got you gotta you gotta I mean I'm already getting vibes off your shit. Can you focus with me?
Mm-hmm. Look into his eyes look into his eyes. Hi white dog
If I focus back
I mean, let me throw one out.
This one here is going to be, holy shit.
You, what do you try to, you try to like move to like the,
like, I don't know where you live,
but you try to move like to the coast.
You try to like maybe move.
Oh, you already heard me say that earlier.
I did it.
Yeah, because I asked you about your apartment.
You're stupid.
Yeah, I caught you.
Are you actually trying to move to the coast?
Like, so let me, let me, let me go.
Where are you where I mean, where are you trying to move? Oh my gosh. That's why I was asking you about your apartment
Dum-dum
Right near the beach. All right. Oh
Come on man. Let's get back to the car. You have like god damn it at this someone every time
I get one every time with people dude you have
Okay, I don't know if that's you but you have
You're getting attacked
by somebody, like, I don't know if it's your, like,
your fucking, it's not your family, it's your fucking...
I know, he'd be a good reader if he could.
You're like hiding, but your wife is getting harassed
by like her mom, I guess, is that it, is that it?
No, I don't have a wife and nobody's getting harassed.
Nope, I don't have a girlfriend.
You don't have a girlfriend right now?
No.
But no, they're okay the other time man. You were like you had did you have one you have a girlfriend?
You were on with my aunt
My aunt okay, and fucking that was like whoa. What the fuck?
Are you drunk? Well, no you have you have a couple sisters like right now I have like
No, I have to oh
Yeah
Yeah, here's the thing there. Did you there's somebody else that like passed away? Oh
You're doing my aunt. I know
He's getting a message stop like you're like your sisters are like
Are like arguing about somebody that is it's not alive anymore. No, they actually don't talk to each other
Well, they were because they hate each other
Oh, is that where you switch it around?
Okay, well you had there was a there was like sorry. Okay. This is done
What I don't think you're just not it's not working out Chris. What are you talking about?
It's not working
Let me move on to the next. I can't believe I consider doing chatter. They would just do the next card
I don't know this this one is like you're you're trying to find you try you want to you want to go to a
Oasis in
But what's that like isn't that like anybody? Oh wait, they want everybody knows. Oh, I mean fuck
I what a little I've been away since right here in Vegas. I go I could walk down the street get my dick set for 50 bucks
Oh my god, I always just I get drunk 24-7. No, no last call
You know me. I ain't tried to go to anyway, you know
Inside scoop on fucking gambling and fucking get money what my oh
That's weird you have to pay for it man. That's fucking weird. Hey fucking money money makes a world-turn type shit
You know me doesn't know you can look good too and fucking have pretty girls
What are you doing?
You what do you want? You know anyways, like I said, you want to move the you know, you were looking for pleasure. Let me go
No, I'm not looking you deny you've denied you know, so you fucking you deny your your religion
Like I don't know you're not religious anymore. You used to be he denied his religion, right?
Yeah, Satanist
So what religion were you so you fuck you gave up on it. You're like fucking well
Why don't you tell me you have the cards? What religion was I I mean
Catholic
No, come on. I mean you was and it still is the Satanist
Hello, dude. Are you serious?
You know, I mean like what but here's the thing you
You have you have a you get your beliefs. Yeah, you gave up you like fuck this like I'm not
But you never gave up my like my complete, you know
My heritage no way. So what are you?
Satanic
That's what I'm saying, bro. So it's all bad for you. You know me
And I'm German by the way
Yeah, I mean fuck you say about German dude, like what do you think about, you know, ever African Americans?
Don't I would never marry one
makes brief bad bad bad genetics
Right, right
Okay
Who is that you don't know same name wait wait wait hold on a minute. Hold on going back to that
I want to
Wait, they kick in a certain way. I would never marry one if you fish is or have a kid with one
but
best friends with
A fucking black guy, and his daughter looks up to me like I'm an uncle.
So that's cool.
Well, like here's the thing, like you have, I just don't believe, I don't believe in mixing.
That's my problem.
Yeah, like I listen I don't want my kid to be in like a you know, what's it called?
You know in an elementary school like fucking the retard school like fucking you know me like that's why I don't want to mix read
Are you stupid are we retarded anyway? We're in the u.s. Are we all kind of mixed?
No, like my fucking like the white race is the best fucking race did the fucking the breathe with
Wow, I mean it's facts fool. It's facts. Yeah, I don't mean to say
you know what I mean but fucking dummy like you get i mean it does sound like you know the
short like oh my kids like you know you know but uh but i love my wife but my kids like retarded
like fuck are you stupid like don't get in that situation i'm not going that far next question
but then you don't you know you know somebody that's like far away from you i don't know if it
Like I said, they're hiding like hiding like some of you know, like he's trying to let me talk number one
Like I said
The guy that I know he's a black and I grew up with him and he was one of my best friends and
fucking his daughters
like call me on the phone and
Hey, uncle Aaron
And yeah, that's my name and fucking I'm like, hey, what are you guys doing?
but
What I get with like his sister. No
Never this is this crazy
Okay, go ahead once I guess
It's like is that now or is that an old video? That's an someone sent me just on me that that was I guess he was getting a reading on
On a Ziggy was getting a reading on clumsy from Chris K. It was kind of a little bit of an interesting reading
So I've never seen white
What kind of readings, like psychic readings?
Well, he was doing his tarot, but he's like,
and he's like, oh, you have some sisters,
and your sisters hate each other, and your aunts dead,
but it's like, he's like,
all this like, I don't know if that's like cards,
or what, I mean, if he's getting the spirit messages
or something like that, it's been okay.
I mean, he did a reading for Alex once,
she said it was okay, like he's done a reading
for me before, but I've seen him do
probably some of the worst readings I've seen,
but
Okay, it's it's still it's still funny. I mean it's like so really I mean it's really as comedic value
And that's a value to me
I'm doing good. I mean I was out and then come home and I see Brandon upset
I have a real life though
I do real life and and I feel better that way because if this stuff is toxic
I'm done with the flip-flopping back and forth back and forth and oh you're a good person
And then you're a bad person because you want to be involved in this
All the girls came home and and I saw him upset and he called me and we talked and you know I
calmed him down I mean we've gotten to be friends and he's very sensitive so I don't understand
his flip-flopping and I'm upset because Alex decided to put salmon on and he always wants
to make it about me when he doesn't even know me he doesn't know the truth
You know, maybe you need to see all sides of everybody because I have a lot of proof that I'll put out there
And so did the ex-brands of this person. I'm talking about about Vita
Yeah, I mean I think I mean the Alex take it like you know allowing him on because she had a topic
You know her topic was talking about Carl and
You know and even like and Brandon, I guess maybe he wanted to fight with Sam and or something
I mean, I guess he did because he just like left ones when the show or whatever
But you know, but we know Alex runs her show a certain way and it's like
Yeah, and it's like I wouldn't just go up there and like, you know
Randomly and then have you know, I don't know she likes to have her
Her he knows that salmon is full of shit. We talked about it
I mean look he lost his channel because we all reported him
It wasn't crystal that took him down. I even got an email back from them
Did it succeeded because I also was was reporting him and I used the steps on the somebody showed me to do to the GT
Chat or whatever and as soon as you put that information in there boom. It's gone
And then you get a response so uh crystals trying to take credit for it, but it was a bunch of people that been reporting him
Okay, you know and then and then she knows that we can't stand him and she's gonna bring him in when I was you know
When she's talking about us and he doesn't even know me
He's listening to a crazy bitch that was 51 52 times and lost all her friends years ago
And they were ready. They were ready to join panel to speak up
But that they weren't gonna go talk against her though because they were friends with her before it wasn't gonna be about beta
It was gonna be about Barb
And crystal, you know, that's what it was going to be about not not their ex-friend
Beta so I don't like this and her hinting. Oh, well you said somebody said you said this before
Yeah, we would she said a lot of shit about me too me and Alex went back and forth and
I have communication from a certain person sending me all this stuff to go to this court against
Alex and I've had that I keep my text everything is saved
You know because you never know
Well, I'm done with this and they're all they're both lonely went in my lonely
I'm always out with friends, you know, I don't need to work ever, you know
And she didn't mean that in like, you know in a hurtful way or whatever. I mean, you're like lonely
I'm never lonely and plus I got these pets and
A friend of mine brought a cat that she has and you got sick and at least I contacted somebody that knows more
And she gave me some kind of drops for the cat is helping
So the lady's gonna pick up the cat tomorrow cuz she didn't know what to do
You know, so I get busy with that. So I wasn't even online, you know, except for this morning before I left
I saw
Her being very compliment complimentary towards you. I did she didn't get lonely. It's like lonely. Why cuz I
Know me call me lonely, too
I mean, we all because I mean, it's I really wasn't in a malicious way that she said yeah, I've never been loud
I wish I was left alone sometimes, you know, I got my pets and it's it's hard sometimes
Especially when you got neighbors and they don't know what to do about a pet or cat or
you know because I got them all involved with the rescue so I get busy over here I was out till
2 30 in the morning last night trying to help somebody find her cat uh that somebody said
they thought it got hit by car but I found the cat you know and then I brought it was like 2 30
and I had to take a little um a carrier in a towel I didn't want to be scratched or anything
You know so I get busy and then I left I was finally able to go out and stuff
And then came back to this and it's like, you know, all I did was talk to Brandon and he said very sensitive though
Psyche, he's a good guy. I know I see that part of him
And I don't think he's a bad person and I saw even he was very disrespectful to her when he came on her show
He said go suck on Samans dick. I mean, that's what he that's the first thing he said to her
Yeah, I just I just saw that I didn't even see there cuz I had just gotten home before I I saw him upset
And then we were talking cuz I didn't know what was going on
You know because she is I've got my family around and sometimes it's just they get on my nerves like they come over or whatever
You know and and I mean and and you know and she's got her mom too. She's she's lucky
And I went all out for her to talk to Tommy because she was really upset
You know and I helped with that and then she's gonna do this and let that asshole salmon jumped on panel
Knowing that he's always going to go at us. He's a piece of shit. He's bad as hell.
Yeah, it doesn't shut down any of that. I mean, I've seen her be very protective of you.
And I know that, um, you know, she, he had something to say about the Carl situation.
And, you know, it's sometimes-
Well, he was trying to make it about me. It was nothing.
Yeah, you're right. But she didn't let him. She didn't let him. And she said-
Yeah.
She said, she said, she said, stop talking about grateful. She's a great-
You know first and her friend and you're not gonna call her names. No, she didn't say much of that
I don't know what she said, you know
That one I just saw the last one
And she doesn't know me and I had my friend
I mean I say I just want to say like she really does like she cares about you she cares about him
she has a good heart about it and I mean it's like he even yeah but she flip flopped so fast
with the the worst people ever and that worst person is saman who's fake as hell and we're so
face oh I mean and she understands that but I think it's a sign of like intelligence actually to
be able to talk to somebody maybe that you have a big differences with and it's like and you know and
she um has been having some good conversations with people that
you know historically maybe yeah but she knows it's bad with him because he's obsessed with me
and kkk can't get rid of him uh she says he's desperately trying to get communication with him
and he's over there oh they're old old or whatever his mama was old and look at her what she looked
like they sent me her real picture in their facebook so yeah it's it's stupid
But you know all I do is fight back and and she knew better. I can't stand that man
I can't stand that thing
It's her show and it's like whoever she wants to have on yeah
It's like it's it's okay. And then Brandon shouldn't expect
Oh, he wants to be on the put on the show on his conditions to say this to this person when I didn't know that
He hung up because she said okay, I'm gonna talk to my intern right now
I don't want you on the line together
I don't want to you know that you to fight so I'm just gonna talk to him and then Brandon got mad because he wanted to fight with
Sam and that was the whole thing it started so he hung up and right away
He's like oh fuck her fuck her because she didn't let me on the air
I mean, that's what it was about started and then he kind of like and I know he has a temper and he kind of went
Right, and he started bad-mouthing me and started bad-mouthing her and it's like and we're you what why you
I said, oh, what do you do you go watch psyches stupid AI music and
And you know in psyche never did anything for me and Alice never did anything for me
They're just kissing all you know the all our enemies butts and stuff
and and
I really went to bathroom and so does she I mean like
Psyche his chat was horrible. They were attacking him even that locale
Streamer who I thought I was cool with because that's my favorite streamer
And he's over there sending nasty messages from her the way he said it was nasty and
Samans all in there with all the counts attacking him
I'm a mod. So I'm the one that
Hid them from his channel to stop harassing him and it's all over whatever happened with her and
And that's going to get you know people will jump in because they see like a weakness or maybe like
Messages from from a couple of her ex the people that she was trying to be cool with recently already tell me see
I told you what happens, you know, and I don't like that. Yeah, but yeah, they try to
mean they jump in trying to like, you know
Cause cause cause dissension in the rings or whatever, right? Yeah
Yeah, and thank you Patrick. Thank you. I do put a lot of work into the things I make and it's like I
Wanted learn to do those so AI stuff like with dogs and stuff little videos. That's what I want to do
I can help you with that too. Yeah, I'm really happy to help people like and it's like, you know
It's a whole it's a whole world you can get into and it's like, you know, and just kind of do whatever
You know strikes you
It's so cool and it's like
And it's like, you know Alex
It really inspires me and taught me a lot and give me some direction.
And she's like, you know, she's also like, you know, she's a really caring person.
She's trying, she's trying to help us, you know, and it's like, you know, it's kind
of like he's a little bit like kind of like, you know, you know, those dogs that sometimes
they've been at a previous, a previous owner and they've been mistreated and stuff.
And then it's like, you know, someone like comes over and like, you know, feeds them
and stuff.
And then, but then the dogs sometimes snaps because it gets back into its old.
mindset and is like a distrustful thing.
I mean, she really, she didn't do anything
to have him say, oh, go suck Sam as,
she wasn't sucking Sam as you should watch the interview.
I didn't see that part, I only saw the last
and then she still did a status.
I don't even know, yeah, go ahead.
Really me?
No, she's lonely.
You know i mean again she was like she said uh she said you know and she said i think you know
They're they're they're good together because they probably might have some loneliness and she's like she's like no
She's the one that told me to support him
I didn't know him and we got to become friends because he lives in albuquerque and i went there to
You know, when I started, well, I went to boarding school overseas, but then we came
back to the states and, you know, I went to school there in Albuquerque.
And so he's familiar, because he went and checked out our old home and he said it was
nice and stuff.
So I gave him the address and asked him, how does it look now?
Well, my brother took pictures because he was there a year ago.
But uh, yeah, that's it. It's it's I'm not on here all the time. Sure. And I'm not gonna
I'm here I'm here for I'm here for I'm here not like just like cuz I'm lonely, but it's like that's like, you know
It's like I would be
person with yeah she doesn't know us she's lonely you know i mean we all have a loneliness too i
think i don't maybe it was an empathy instead of like uh i don't know yeah it's like sometimes i wish
i was alone sometimes you know just yeah well i know but sometimes we can be like surrounded by
people and still feel lonely you know like that's part yeah like friends or neighbor like neighbors
it's like damn it's just in a way i'm thinking god leave right yeah we're right it's like sometimes
but it's like then at the same time, it's like, you know,
it's like nothing worse than being around a lot of people
and still feeling lonely, which is like so-
Yeah, no, it's like she doesn't even know me.
I don't understand, but-
I mean, it's like, you know,
you've known each other for a few years, but I think that-
Not really, I didn't know her.
I think we went at it most of the time, but I like her.
You know, she's funny.
I know she has worked with you, and it's like,
I really don't want anything to fracture between you.
And it's like, I know what I'm saying,
Like what she was kind of picking up like you have a real maternal energy towards Brandon like I'm and it's nothing
I'm not it's like no, yeah, he's younger than me. Yeah, he says we're friends though
It's not it's not a maternal or anything. We just vibe as friends. I don't know
And they're like mom like cuz that's like, you know, I know
I know I know but I'm making an analogy
I'm saying like, you know, he kind of like goes to you and it's like and he he knows he gets like that
understanding and sympathy from you and you provide that too and it's like if you feel it towards
him more because if he's a younger man and it's almost like a like a small no because I can read
people especially after a lot of things that I've been through growing up you know I just
and then living overseas all my life and you know so I
I felt bad because he's a good person when you get to know him. I think you know that
I never disagreed with that and it's like but um, and but then again
I'm he did like kind of lash out at me and I kind of in them into her too in a really immature way
And it's like I'm saying it's immature because I think that it's something that can be
grown out of or dealt with in his I mean it's like but like really it's like you
know he's not a perfect person he's the world nobody is I'm not there nobody
and he was like he's not about her son about psyche he's like psyche wouldn't
have anybody if it wasn't for me that well I actually lost a lot of people
because I would platform him you know it's like and so not it's like and then
he's like oh cuz I just have stupid AI music
Well, it was like, you know, I mean, I like your music.
I like the music.
OK, so we have.
So do you want to tell you so you don't want to discuss anything
with Sam Mann or you do?
No, no, he's a piece of shit, man.
It's all he doesn't even know me.
He doesn't know me and he's going to say all this shit about me.
No, I don't want anything to do with him.
OK, but this guy.
Yeah, he's fine.
I like the background.
That's 300.
Yeah, okay. I don't have beef. I don't have drama. I don't have AIDS either. I mean, that's the new thing and now it's like
Nobody likes getting drunk or what everybody starts acting weird and I'm out of alcohol unfortunately
Yeah, what was going on in the stream yard world everybody just judging each other like I don't know what happened today
I don't know
Grateful, so you won't talk to Sam and you would you know, I don't want anything to do with him
All he wants to do is fight and he doesn't even know the truth. There's two sides to the story though
You know and I've shown my proof
So no, I don't need to talk to him because it's the same thing
Back and forth. He's still using an old picture of me when people have seen me
I don't want any communication with them at all. Okay. I don't want anything
And so I'll wait till I wait till you're off until I bring him up. Okay. Yeah, well, of course, he's gonna talk shit about me, you know
Beyond psyches channel psyche wants to see you react to them so go ahead and
You have all the right
Well, I have all the right to bring him up
Okay, as long as
Hello salmon salmon. Hey, don't do talk to me like that. What what what shit about people they know like to confront them
What do you mean you who's talking shit? You're the one that you talking shit cuz you
To you no, she wasn't he just said she wasn't I'm done with the drama, Sam and I'm not talking about
Shit about me fuck you
Sam and I and I'm done with that. I want to be done with it. I know
You exposed her. Yes, it was cool. Who?
Yeah
I did not she's lying to you
Are you kidding? You're saying she lies about everything. You're so cool with her though. I'm not cool with her
I don't have anything to do with her. No
Yeah, because the last time I was on panel
I just said li it, you know, let's just we agreed to leave each other alone and that was that and I was very nice about it
Sam
What you were talking about Kate what you okay? What picture that berry said?
About red balloon is something bro. These girls are gonna
Yeah, i'm not i'm not doing anything
Oh, yeah niggas i don't give a fuck nigga
Yeah, I'm just done with all of it right now. What the drama? No, I don't know Sam and I don't and you know
I mean, we're all no seriously. I don't know you laughing at like that
You know, I'm laughing because it's stupid. You know, I was a part of it, too
All of us were and I just don't want to continue that I don't like getting triggered
You know, you get triggered too and we don't get triggered and tell people to get raped. That's you that was years ago
That was 20
told me no no that to you I didn't say I wanted you to get hurt
I got right then when I was a child. Oh, I don't remember saying that. I would have said it
Yeah, yeah, I probably said it out of anger because of what you
You know what Sam and I'm gonna apologize to you for now
You know, I don't want to keep on with his hate because when you and KK went live together and you know, you guys
No, you guys were
No, I'm not because KK was good. You guys were good. You had
I don't know
Okay, fuck that bitch
They had a great lives. It was interesting. It was funny and you know, there was not attacking people and I mean it was awesome
They were way better than the owls like
There you go. I mean, it's like she has a good review of your salmon. No, it's true
They were great together. They were great together. It's the Brennan Q Greg get along gang radio
Brandon doesn't like me well since when you suck in his dick
I never sucked as dick in my life. Yeah, you did mad times. Oh my god, brandy Q brandy Q
No, you did them even with the evidence you didn't care
Yeah, you did I did Sam. I remember that when I sucked it. You didn't care. You didn't care now. You look at you
You remember your channel was popping and all that look at you channel now. Well, not because you be you
Of course not you're doing not me
I
Know I'm not I swear to you I'm not no I'm on a panel anyway. No, I don't have the
Then wait till later and you'll see that you're wrong
I'd be posting it. No, I'm not recording
Like like I'm gonna be
Then we all are right
I mean we all behave that way I guess big elder if you want to donate for reading
No, he gave you so much money already, right? Excuse me. Is that in your business?
Don't treat your donate is right
Excuse me. You're now you're talking about my doing it. Do I ever get into your chat about oh, yeah, you complain about donations
No, what I mean, I mean you make the money from me
You don't tell me about my own show get out of here out of here. Oh, what a terrible person
What happened?
Were y'all beefin' or something?
No, he told me to shut the fuck up and stuff.
I don't like to be told that on my own show.
And he also was like, oh, I was sucking off Brandon's dick.
And I was like, excuse me, I'm Sam Man's hook a lot more than Brandon's.
No, no, no, I never did anything with Brandon.
Sam Man, I woke up with this hook in my mouth.
Yeah, now I didn't even know what happened between you and Brandon. I guess you
I mean it was it was like, you know, just he was calling me
A few times he'd call me stupid and idiot and then insulted my music and like, you know, oh, you know
You should or tell me oh, you should do this or I'm a target. I'm this I'm this I'm this
And it's like and I all I did was like really try to help him and put myself on the line for him a few times
And you know, and he really didn't appreciate it and it's like, you know how your name is grateful
I was just thinking like, you know, you have gratitude and all Alexander has gratitude
I have gratitude and it's like and that really is like
But he's not grateful.
And I think it's maybe his age and maybe like being young, immature, maybe like a little bit.
He's probably been through a lot, you know.
I know.
I have been the first one to say, I say, I understand trauma and stuff has happened.
And it's like, and then he's been bullied and all this stuff.
But all this stuff has happened to me, too.
Like, and it's happening to me now.
It's happening to me now.
And it's like, you know, maybe even more than, you know.
to him a little bit. Sometimes it's like, you know, right now. So it's like, you know,
I can't go where I mean, it's like, and I know it's bad for him. So that's where the empathy
comes in, right? But it's like, at the same time, I don't like to be called. I mean, we
should be, if we're going to be on each other's team, we got to be on each other's team, at
least if you know, tell me privately, I don't agree with this decision. I don't agree with
that decision. No, say in front of everybody, Oh, you're stupid. And, you know, and you're
Give him a chance to you know shine a little bit and and I just because I was because we because we want to run on our shows
A different a different way or a certain way
We I mean every content creator should be that Brandon has his own platform if salmon was born there and argue with Brandon
Salmon will go. I mean it's like but it's like you know, it's like she doesn't want
The show her show would be Jerry's spring or all of a sudden in the middle. Yeah, right
With their own beeps, right and so
She really she was good
She came on like you should you should watch that whole episode where she was like giving her every opportunity to think about it
And then it's like, you know, she let him on and then you know
And she kind of you know, she read him and and and roasted about just a little bit, you know
it's just just to kind of wake him up I would say and
gave him and then he gave him a chance to come up and like then immediately he goes
Something about suck sandman's dick and then she takes him off and then she's like well
I'm gonna give you one more chance
You owe me an apology and he said I'm not gonna. I don't owe you shit. I don't owe you apology
But and so she I mean that was it and it's like and then she still said
We'll talk to you in seven days. She she wants him to
Progress a little bit and it's like I think you can help with that. You come in
She said you calm him down. You have a calming voice. You have a good relationship with him. She likes how you talk to him
Right and it's like and then she and she doesn't you know, she talks to very few people personally or whatever
Not many on from here I've learned my lesson
But there's a couple of all three people I talked to and we've always talked and
One of them is special
She's like a daughter to me and you know, she's not part of any of this stuff and that's what I like about her
Right, you know, she brings me down off of this drama and stuff sometimes because she's always doing real life
Like she doesn't know what's going on and and that helps me though, too
We laugh and talk about pets and she's involved with veterinary chair and
It gives me good advice, you know, for the rescues and stuff, and that's what I like,
and it's showing me her e-bike, and, you know, we have real convos, and she's never been a part of
this, but she finally agreed that she was going to join a panel.
And now I'm glad that this happened and so I can tell you know what it's not worth it
Like you said it's better just to stick with real life, you know, and we
Yeah, I mean it's like I mean there's there's friends you can make but it's like you're gonna have your cat
She looks like mine. I got two of them. The bully looks like your cat that one
That's Lenore the is a bully. Yeah. Yeah. It's a black cat looks innocent, but she's a bully
She's unlike the other cats and gives them all a hard time and she thinks I'm all hers
And when they all come close to me, she's she starts growling like my dog. She does like my dog though
That's like Lenore. Lenore like, you know, because lola always is uh on my lap and stuff and then Lenore will just like stare at us or like staring at
Yeah, yeah
And then but but the bully when she sees me get upset. She'll paw at me like hey mommy
You know I'm here. You know, she's so cute. I think she's like my guard cat. They all are
Yeah, oh my gosh, I get like a yeah, I get a lot of like a guard
Guardian energy with the cats like in this cat. Yeah, they're very protective. I didn't know that about cats
Yes, you look at it. Is it a he or she is Lenore? She's a girl Lenora. Oh good girl. No one there's a look at that beautiful face
Yeah, they're so sweet and you know, that's that's what I love about them. They don't yell. They don't use people
They don't yell
I always spank when they're like this and good times is like don't spank your cat. Let's hit it your cat
Thank you. They like that. That's good for their
Little bit on her butt. Yeah
if they didn't like they cats don't like something they will let you know they do don't they and dogs too
they'll like make a sound or they'll like you know or you know cats will just you know
they will not be on your lap they'll be like oh leave me alone you know cats sometimes they
like people that don't like cats because the people like weird mine mine try to get on my lap and they
fight over with each other to you know because they want to be with me it's just so weird it's just
yeah all of them and they sleep with me with my dog and yeah they're and usually cats are off to
themselves people tell me and no not them they're always with me
Yeah, well, that's miss Lenora. She likes to go. So how old is Lenora?
Lenora's I think probably four years old and I have a picture of baby
There's a baby picture that was probably taken when I first got her because I think I got about maybe four years ago
Almost exactly. Oh, sometimes I'll send you pictures of mine or their their baby pics. I think this is yeah
This is Lenora right here Lenora and then Lola looks like kitty kitty was almost 21 years old
And she passed away a couple months ago
One time she went out and she got lost and I couldn't find her for like three days and then she just seemed slow like she was slowing down already though, you know, and I took her to the vet and they said there was nothing more they could do for her.
And she was just slowing down and all and you know see but oh my god, it's heartbreaking though
She's yeah, your Lola looks this like her. That's why I want to get another cat that looks just like her
Yeah
Like Rudy's you know, he's 17 or 18 years old, so he's like slowing down a lot and
Yeah, they do it's yeah, I didn't think she'd be if she'd be gone. It's like she like she'd get confused and
Sleep in the dark sometimes and just seem confused and I don't like she didn't recognize
the other cats or me sometimes and
It was just and then she passed away
I'm sorry.
Oh, yeah.
Fucks.
But yeah, she was my baby.
She was the first cat I rescued in because of her, you know, that's how she was the one
that was fascinated with my pecanesis and she joined our walks and they became celebrities.
Neighbors were taking pictures and videos of her walking with them.
And they'd freak out is like wow look at that cat walking with the dogs. I can't look at acts like it. It's a dog
My cats on like harnesses and stuff and they just like will sit down
They don't want to or you don't want me to lease your harness really but yeah
The fact that you can like take yours out and it walks along with the dog
They walk along with them. They don't they don't yeah, they don't run away or anything. There's no harness
I try to put a harness on kitty one time and she just froze
Yeah, they don't want to be walked, but they'll walk and I mean they don't want to walk with them.
But yeah, they'll walk with you and stuff.
And she walked right ahead of them, like she was showing everybody,
look at me, this is my family, you know, and people be taking videos and pictures.
I have a couple cats, or a cat that she would follow me to...
the Whole Foods and then she'd sit outside a Whole Foods while I was inside and then wait
Uh-huh, and then also the same at the liquor store
She just sit outside the liquor store and then walk down streets across
Yeah, like a photos follow me home like the whole way. I was like don't get lost
But yeah, yeah, but kitty did that sometimes when I'd cross the street with my dogs
She just fly up on the fence and you know, she I mean, you know, she was quick and get she'd get to us again
But yeah, she but then she'd stay with us
And now these cats do the same thing and you know, we miss kitty
Yeah, so they all walk with me and people are taking pictures and and videos
So they're like celebrities or people's kids even come over. Okay. Can we see the cats?
The ones that that we're walking with your dog and they'll play with them
Yeah
That's what's important to me though. I love them. I love them more than humans
They don't they don't judge you. They don't care how my nails look. They don't care, you know, they just care, you know
They're loved and
And but they're there for you like when you feel sick like last year when I was getting sick
It's like they knew something was wrong. Yeah
They're great supporters and they're great
Healers they're great healing energy the problem they per and they get next to you and they just say
They said it's very soothing, you know, so yes, it's true
But yeah, they're special
God sometimes I'd rather hang out with them than human beings
But I've got some good friends like my best friend is my neighbor and we've got everybody involved in rescue including her mom
You know who does a lot. She knows how to take care of the newborns like we found some newborns and they kept them to feed them and and you know
Because they were the I think the mother cat passed away
Then they were by themselves outside
So now now they're adopted, but they kept them for a while and they even showed me how to how to take care of them with the
lamp light
the heat and
Yeah, and the what is it that food that you feed them? It's for babies
Yeah
With the PDLI or like the milk one the milk. Yeah, it's it no the drops first the drops because they were newborns and now
They're drinking regular milk, but at first they were she was using those drops
It's a special milk or something for them
And then you have to keep the light on for a while because they can die without the light because they were like newborns and the mother
Passed away. They did a great job
No, I had three I've had three litters of kittens. Oh my god
Yeah, I had like two in a year and then I had like one the next year like Lola had one the next year
But then the two litters one of them four survived and then one of them two survived and
it's quite an experience and then and then Lola or Lola's all survived like oh she had five kittens
four males one female and they all survived but as soon as they got as soon as they got big enough
She like she didn't want to deal with them anymore. She kind of like was feeding off me, but then she
Now she likes, you know, but now I've done they're all gone
I mean tux came back for a little bit
But now yeah, he's gone again, but I mean he'll come back
I just like he just like the cats just run around different places in this neighborhood and stuff
But I mean, these have been here like, you know, and I've had it between like three and, you know, 10 cats.
But that was because I had like five cats in a day, five new cats.
And so, you know, it's like they don't always like to live in such close quarters.
Some of them like to be.
You know single pets and stuff. Yeah, I guess kitty after that's what she got decided because she's she's a bully now
She's getting a little bit better, but sometimes she'll still act up
You know like this is my mommy is you know, I'm the only one getting attention get out of here
You know and then she'll his at them
Did you see that video I sent you of the gorilla in the cat like that?
That you see that one I said I posted you I don't know if you saw that one, but oh, okay
Did you when did you send it a new one or because I'd like to
Video but yes, yes, okay. Yes, I have that I love it
Yeah, yeah, and I just found something that I posted before with a lot of peeking eases and and that's like heaven
I just posted it in my shorts
I want to see if you like this one real quick because this is when I haven't shown you this one
I just showed on the show the other night, but this is like so cute. It's a short little short
Video on I think it's called this channel is called the dodo or something like that. Yeah, I like that
Yeah, the dodo. I think I'm subscribed to that. Uh-huh. Let me see if I probably find it on my on my board or on my
hosts because let me, oh no it's not my posts, I know where I have it on my phone calls, hold on,
because I want to get you the exact clip, but this is okay, so this is like a squirrel, the squirrel's
name is Nuts, and then the cat's name is, let me see, the cat's name is Cheeto, okay, and my friend
And let me use this link.
Okay, I hope you love this, okay?
Here.
I love everything with cats, dogs, all kinds of animals.
Well, I think you will enjoy this.
Okay, pace and go and...
I got a bunch of them on my Instagram.
Whoa some other stuff on Instagram some other cool stuff. So here's here you go
Here's your chick this out
Kidding means baby squirrel and immediately falls in love
Who fell in love with this girl
The kid in oh Cassie. Oh my god
I'll rewind it. Hold on. I'm ready to take the cat
Yeah, check this out.
The first time I introduced nuts and Cheeto,
I thought closely watch them.
Yeah, if not too often, you see a squirrel and a cat.
I'm ready to take the cat if anything happens.
Hey, what do you think?
Oh, how'd you look at the squirrel?
Cheeto started to lick his fur like he was one of his siblings.
He'll clean your face.
He's going to clean you.
and nuts had this look on his face like what are you doing buddy so what happens
well they didn't care one was a squirrel and one was a cat
nuts would play with him and snuggle with him they're gonna grow up to be best friends
at that moment i thought okay is this relationship gonna be something that lives on forever
Well, I am NOT a cat person. I've always had big dogs actually
But about two months ago my wife and I went to go meet Cheeto
Come here. Okay. Oh
I instantly fell in love
We already had a dog at home Ruger. He's like an old man
So I was worried about how Cheeto would react because he was only nine weeks old at the time
Look at the dog's eyes
He's like what's that Cheeto was actually the one who walked up and I'm like oh my gosh
He's going right up to him
But Ruger just kind of ignored him
So we put Ruger away in his bedroom and Cheeto kind of hangs out with us
Until one night. I couldn't find Cheeto anywhere
He's in here with a worker sleeping on him.
Oh.
He's not enjoying this.
But she's...
I'm like, huh?
What did she tell him, love?
And from that moment on, I'd see them slowly getting
comfortable with one another.
But then, all of a sudden, nuts came into our life.
Nuts? I like that name.
We were taking Ruger on a walk.
I looked down on the ground, and there was this little,
tiny squirrel.
I said, hey, little guy, come here.
Well, a squirrel just walked into my hand.
I felt like Nuts chose me to be his new dad.
Yep, that's a squirrel in my pocket.
I actually went back the next day
to see if I could see any squirrels.
And so I went online, and I researched how can I
rehabilitate and help raise this squirrel.
You so hungry?
Cheeto was honestly the first one to accept nuts.
At night Cheeto would just sit by Nuts' house and just stare and like touch it with his feet like he wanted to play.
And then they'd chase each other a little bit.
And I think it was very important at the time of their life where they bonded.
But for now I think Nuts' place is to live outside in the trees.
So I made his little house put it in the tree, and I say okay. Here you go buddy. This is your new home
And he just jumped in it, and I was just like okay. I think he likes it
Where are you nuts?
It was bittersweet honestly
But then when it was time for nuts to go Cheeto and Ruger they had already connected it now Cheeto
He's a copycat
If Ruger lays down in his bed, what happens?
Cheeto comes and lays right next to him.
They just kind of inseparable.
Oh, how adorable.
Everything worked out really perfectly, right?
That's beautiful.
Like that.
I have one more little short thing for you.
Because this is a...
Do you like chickens?
Yeah, I do we yes, okay. You like this one. You like this. Okay
Okay, so one second that got bad boy breeze. He raises chickens too. Yeah, I mean he's got chickens
Yes, he would he would do yeah at home. He would always show him on sometimes when he'd make videos
Cool. Yeah, I think these people aren't aren't
India or something like that and they make these videos if you have to get to see it
I mean, it's like it's unbelievable. I mean just get to it real quick. I'm so sorry. Hold on one second
Okay, so it's like a I guess it's a we get something considered a rooster
Those are loud we we had a rooster outside our house and I remember the effort early in the morning man that they're loud I
Think it was the neighbors it wasn't ours
So you might this is you'll I think you'll get a kick out of this
Here we go
This is I guess in India and this is the rooster the cat and
The duck okay, here we go. Oh
That's how cute
That's a lot of hair
You'd have to groom that cat
I want to sleep with the cat he says yeah he wants to sleep in the in the duck is saying
okay oh no the duck is mad stop arguing they're fine over the cat yeah let's live in harmony
Look at the cat just chillin
Right on top of the cat
Is it not good to sleep?
Here comes a duck
Yeah, wait, yeah, yeah
some chicken
Rooster, yeah
There it comes. Oh my god.
Look at the cat's face.
The cat's a pimp, right?
Don't hug the duck to sleep.
Oh, wow, he's hugging the duck.
Look, imagine that rooster waking them up in the morning.
Yeah.
With all that roostering.
Right.
I bet it will start.
Uh-oh. Look at the duck's eye.
That's so cute. Yeah, it's so comfy and they trust the cat.
The chicken now looks like the rooster.
Yeah, the rooster is just still jealous.
Look at the rooster looking at the duck.
Get out of here.
Uh-oh, more chickens are gonna join.
Oh, here goes the dog.
The cat. The cat is looking for more people to sleep with.
Not right now, a cat and a cow.
Oh, no, there's a cow. There goes a cow.
Yeah.
Poor cat is never gonna be able to sleep.
They've been joining the cat.
What the hell?
They only slept for an hour.
Doug is so uncomfortable. Look at the chicken.
I know, right? Look at it.
I'm a little unhappy today.
Yeah, because he's jealous. He wants the attention for himself.
He wants to catch himself.
Oh my god.
Yeah, that's a huge channel.
I remember one of the first ones I watched
that that was like, you know, this like,
I think it was like a cat couple
and one of the cats is like, I'm flying out of town
and then the cat goes out of town
and then their cat is like sleeping in the bed
and then all the animals in the barn yard slowly
turns into the room and sleep with the cat.
And also there's ones where all the chicks
are eating off the cat.
There's ones where all the cats are falling in the cat.
It's so cute, yeah.
That's adorable.
Y'all don't see my stories on IG, especially
punched the monkey that was abandoned by its mother and had a rough time in the zoo and
now look at him, he's friendly and he's big brother to the newer babies that were born
because he didn't have nobody, he didn't have anybody.
The mom rejected him and they had to buy him a stuffed orangutan monkey to take with
him.
He was so little that stuff, it was bigger than him and he carried it around.
And now he's got got accepted by the bigger monkeys and now he loves those babies
But yeah, I follow him every day and I always share a story every day from from him. He's gotten a little bit bigger
But he's adorable, but yeah, so yeah, so see my stories. I like those send them to me sometimes because
I want to I want to follow
So, yeah, well, I'm gonna go ahead and head to bed. I get a wake up early in the morning. So yeah, thank you
You know for having me up and you have a good night
Okay, but make sure what make sure to watch the screen after you hang up because I'm gonna play one more thing on the screen
So what make sure you watch? Yeah. Yeah, okay. I'll watch done in chat. Okay? Okay. Good night. Okay. Let me see if I can find it
I just know
There's this there's this National Geographic show. Yeah, this is it. I found it or no is on the BBC
So they put this they put this baby a fate of a robot
Monkey in the in the forest and so I'll play this before I go. I hope you like this guys. Oh
My gosh, oh the numbers drop so fast. I don't know. Is that a copyright or something? I'm not sure
But here we go my teeth. Okay
Yeah, that was a carrot. Okay, so here we go and having a night guys. This is the I think you'll eat this one
But is it all too good to be true?
The great silver back he won't be so easily impressed
Here he's the boss
Spy gorilla won't be welcomed without his say so
That's spy gorilla
Robot
a warning everyone must stay back can our spy win him over to they await the
silverbacks decision until then there's a line no one can cross his arm a
barrier between them and the newcomer
Yeah, there's these guys.
Decision made.
Spy gorilla.
Can stay.
Uh-oh.
Everyone can relax once more.
Hey guys.
In adults, chest beating is a show of power.
Left or is it right?
For youngsters, it's an invitation to play.
But games easily get out of hand.
Oh my god.
I killed spider monkey.
I know everyone left, I mean, you don't like the animals stuff.
His look says it all.
Best pretended never happened, but it's not the end for our spy.
He lives to film another day.
Okay, guys, well, thanks for coming.
I mean, I've had the TTS set up by tomorrow.
It will be at Colt's, sorry, Coltosecky.com.
If you ever donate to that off the air.
I will make sure to read on the air and play whatever song you request.
Um, I guess, uh, welcome to the Cult of Psyche, I'll see you later on, my friends.
Everything feels safe these days.
The neighbors wave, children play, the sunshine's bright,
the bills get paid, perfect smile's the same.
Well, I was gonna say, I was gonna say like,
fucking, can you just, can't you smell,
like there's a smell on these, these, you know,
Africans like fucking, it's like fucking like,
what the hell are you doing right now, man?
Nothing, fool.
I'm just asking a question.
You're being viewed by a lot of people
Hey guys, hey guys like you know I mean like they they smelled like do you not have to take a shower?
Asshole when you can take a shower like are you stupid like these people are retarded?
I've met a lot of beautiful black women that smell great
Yeah, well fuck me. I haven't but you know, here's the thing. Let me say this like black. I'm trying like clumsy
I know I've tried my hardest to find my tongue
But the fucking don't buy your tongue
There's a lot of like, you know black people like black females that fucking have ass dude like I'm a big ass guy like I fuck
I love that fucking pop that pop that booty. Yeah, I mean, I'm fucking
As I'm hitting that doggy. I mean, I want up, you know, so but they have bought they have fucking body dude like fucking a
Better than they better than what you know, but it's like fuck you gotta you gotta deal with like so you mean better than we know
Said better better than white people is what I said
What is it you have never met a big booty white girl?
Listen, they're
Black people have like some of the best asses dude, like if they're like well then get with her
I've been with the black girl and the black girl. I was wish she did not have any bad body
Yeah, like I don't know what the hell he's talking about
Don't know anything about what he's talking about. I'm just talking about myself. Let me let me read you
No, no, wait, wait, hold on before you continue
There is also since you're so into the white women and you're
You're saying basically that black women have big booties and you wish that white women dead
I that's what I that's what I get with
Like the woman I'm with now
Yeah, big ass
You know you could say that bro, but you don't even come up. So I don't know the belief. I don't like to came up
I just don't and I don't know why you do I let me move on. Let me move on
Okay, I'm not gonna argue
What?
I'm not gonna argue like that. You have you've had an issue with you know, you have you say you say his sisters, right?
Yeah
Well, they uh
Did they acquire money and like lose it or something?
No, not at all.
Nope.
Youngest sister got a house
and the other sister got a boyfriend
which he's now cool with me.
And they went separate ways.
They went separate ways.
Well, it just took off what I was saying.
But yeah, yeah, they did.
But you you're like are you actually are you actually like you think that like global warming is a thing you think
Honestly honest to God man, okay, let's go this way
Fucking you're talking about global warming. You're talking. Yeah, I'm guessing that you're somebody
No, wait, wait, wait. Hold on. Hold on. You're gonna talk about aliens. I don't give a fuck
No, there's somebody in your family that died from some type of lung disease, right?
No.
Bullshit.
There is.
Well.
No.
It might be like, maybe, maybe it's like way back, way, way back, but there's somebody
that this.
Oh my God.
If you're saying like before I was born or something, maybe you're like, you're, you're
in your fucking family, dude.
There's a guy.
I hope you get the name right if it is true like all Oliver or something like that
Nope, you're wrong. We never had an Oliver in our family
No way
Yeah, I want to talk to your fucking you know your mom and your grandpa and you know
Dude if you are willing I would fucking totally let you talk to my mom
But like you know right now
Right now in your life, you feel like you're uh, you're like you like, you know, you're done
You like you finished you've victorious
Mmm, you have a lot of ambition and you're like uh, that's wrong
No, I've been making music and fucking hanging out with my boy and
Fucking we've been both making music right?
Let me go back. Let me go. So this this is like completely wrong
I don't know why sometimes I gotta go back I gotta go back through let me go back
You're talking about birds you were so correct about or talk about a bird like freedom bird free
I'm on you were so correct before
But I don't know how why you're this wrong now
No, you you you said
If you're talking about music, bro, I didn't know that
So you like you
Okay, let me let me think when you talk about fucking birds like flying. Oh
No chickens chickens
Bad birds, yeah, fuck yeah, so you talk about that when you sing music. Um, I
Won't necessarily say it like that man. I'm not like I'm
listen who who who fucking I'll come here girl to a bird though like I'll do
that I mean are you trolling me dude are you being serious I'm being like a
turkey yeah right exactly exactly well then listen that there's somebody that
like where you do that like they passed away like who was the person that passed
Nobody's done no shit
They've been passed away like that their property like where you where you stay is like they did pass away
I don't know. I don't know where the goddamn birds at dude on my property
So maybe you're in somebody that are you trigger wait are you triggering like the people that own the property before me?
Yes, I mean back like way back. Oh, I wouldn't know like
This guy okay, his name was Judd
So who was that the guy that in the property before me was he was your family? No
Are you sure yeah swear to God why what was it with a pink bed?
He like laid in a pink bed. Did you have like some pink fucking sheets or some shit?
No, I don't know no idea
No idea fucking
He's still there the guy the guy's still there. You're whatever whatever house
Well, they're what I will say this like on top of my house like I'm not giving you credit
because like you have failed today but there was like this weird thing man and
I was I don't do math I don't do anything
nothing and I walked out and there was something on top of my fucking roof
yeah and I'm like what the fuck was that
Well, there's that you know, you got to be careful with the roof
but it's because of
Somebody that used to like live there
Maybe that's that Judd guy. I don't know Doug. I don't know
But he's a
He's like still there dude. Be careful. You got some haunted bullshit, bro. Oh
You have no idea like yeah, and and by the way
I'm telling you bro like there's there's there's people that are they that had used to live where you live
You don't understand this like for real
Like I'm I'm even telling like
And these fools are upside down
No, look, I'm telling you this
I write music and fucking when I do and my buddy Jordan comes over and we're both writing
like my door will fucking like slap like like a bolt yeah it's crazy and it's like the door
was locked I'm not joking it's there is somebody that's in a pink clumsy I know that I was
But that's the truth
That is the real know it's somebody that was in a pink bed, bro back in the dark
I don't know early 1900s like 19 like you know 60s or something that whoever had that pad before
Well, whatever it was fucking. I don't know
but
Yeah, oh, yeah
How old is my house now?
Yeah, 1940
Yeah, well this this guy this guy. I don't know. I don't know what his deal is
Why is it? Why is it a dove? What the fuck is the dove a dove burn? I don't know. I don't like doves
Did this person that lived there, I don't know where you live, but he where he lived there and he I
Don't know if he was like in the music, but he had like a yeah, he was in the music. He was in the music
He was in the music. Oh
And he sung something so I don't know who that was
Okay, well, I'm not gonna fight it. I'm not gonna fight. Let me get more deep. I gotta fight it
It wants me to stop cuz I'm getting too deep, but
So pink bed like he had like pink sheets or something I don't know
I told you I don't know that
I don't think he was white. He was like a he had like a
Is it just it fucking okay?
Stalkers dude fucking sucks. Dude Chad is so laughing right now
That's fine, you know me, but you go listen you pad your app, bro. No, no, it's it really
Yeah, I was trying to tell clumsy clumsy are you here you have you have like some you have somebody else
It's like what I'm on your head. It's your fucking pad haunted
That is the truth. Yeah. No, it is. Yeah, okay
Like when I'm like like I want to give you a couple of my lyrics real quick
Is that cool? So all the other cards don't even mean anything, but this is the main one, bro
This guy this guy fucking right here is like fucking. I don't know like can you find out like he like uh
I don't know
No, he's like he's like he's like he like he like lost his air like I don't know if he like what happened how he died
Losses air. I don't know the way he died. He lost his air like he couldn't breathe and he like turned blue
So I don't know what I don't like fucking that's where you live fool. You know me
Well, whatever. I mean I bought the property, you know
Today, you know
If you see any type of like spirits like fucking, you know, just respect them because he there's a guy there that's not about that
Man, it's it. No, I was wanting to talk to you spirit. Fuck you spirit
Clumsy, this is this is a you got to be friendly like you gotta just you gotta adapt
I've never been fucking mean or rude or anything
Um, I wanted to read this to clumsy. Is that cool? Yeah, go ahead
Um, so like we'll fucking be in here, bro
and we'll write shit and
Fucking I write like hardcore and then we'll fucking put a drum machine on and fucking make
You know music or whatever and also you sing you with your mouth. Oh
Well, and yeah, I do of course
But no, he's do his butt for of course. Yeah, I sing through my arm
But um, here's like a part of my lyrics and then this really actually happened
I'm saying spending time with you is such a waste
These hopeless thoughts erased
poorly hidden behind my eyes and then the door slams
That happens every fucking time
right
And that's that listen that that you have like so you have like a you have like a ghost in your shit
Oh, I know I fuck this happened fucking before. Yeah. Oh, yeah
And like my buddy my buddy claims. Well, he's in death metal. I'm not
I'm an industrial metal and
Fucking when he came over he was like, hey man, you're the last guitars
And I'm not a great guitarist, by the way, and I'm like, yeah, dude, I'll fucking like finish off
ma
Sure, but I want to finish fucking death said
Listen, you know, you know, do you know what death said is like fucking is something to do with that pink
pink bed
This guy
Just a thousand whispered stories calling Wanderer's home
Every page of memory, every file burns bright
Ghosts of conversations archive beyond sight to see
Cause in the skeptics the prophets and the fools
Gathered in the codex breaking all the rules
Some came searching answers, some came chasing flame
Some came only wondering why they felt the same
Dreams and strange ideas are fun
Voices carved in code beneath the digital deep
X the signal calls your name
Mystery
Some transcript stories from the edge
Conversations hanging from the razor's head
And led a thousand open panels outcast in the rain
Finding strange connections inside collective pain
Every guest a chapter, every show a thread,
Every strange encounter refuses to stay dead.
The Oracle is watching, learning every tense,
Hidden behind the veil.
Knowledge is an hour, knowledge is a key,
Unlocking hidden chambers inside reality.
We're forgotten dreams and strange ideas are fun.
Thank you for watching!